<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>State-of-the-Art on TheRealMartin&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/tags/state-of-the-art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in State-of-the-Art on TheRealMartin&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/tags/state-of-the-art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mechanistic Interpretability</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/mechinterp/mechinterp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/mechinterp/mechinterp/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Mechanistic Interpretability is the study of reverse-engineering neural networks - analogous to how we might try to reverse-engineer a program’s source code from its compiled binary, our goal is to reverse engineer the parameters of a trained neural network, and to try to reverse engineer what algorithms and internal cognition the model is actually doing. Going from knowing that it works, to understanding how it works.&amp;rdquo;
https://www.neelnanda.io/mechanistic-interpretability/quickstart
An Introduciton to Circuits https://distill.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LLMs Compression | Literature Overview | Our work</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/literature-overview/post-sota-llm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/posts/literature-overview/post-sota-llm/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on a research project on LLMs Compression. Making these models smaller and more efficient. This includes techniques like Pruning, Quantization, and Distillation. The paper will be published mid-2024.
During our research, we gathered over 150 research papers related to state-of-the-art LLMs Compression methods and Optimization. I think this collection is pretty valuable. So here&amp;rsquo;s this massive pile of research for you.
Our work In our research, we address the challenging task of compressing large language models (LLMs) using advanced compression techniques.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
